[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "Was that your understanding?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "that", "your", "understanding", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "Hundred percent.", "answer_tokens": ["Hundred", "percent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "But did you see that side to him?", "question_tokens": ["But", "did", "you", "see", "that", "side", "to", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Never in my company.", "answer_tokens": ["Never", "in", "my", "company", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "Did Oscar have good reason to always fear that somebody may break in and cause him harm?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "Oscar", "have", "good", "reason", "to", "always", "fear", "that", "somebody", "may", "break", "in", "and", "cause", "him", "harm", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "Definitely.", "answer_tokens": ["Definitely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBD", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "And killed her because he was having a human rage?", "question_tokens": ["And", "killed", "her", "because", "he", "was", "having", "a", "human", "rage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "Like said, because, you know, the onus is on -- is on Oscar.", "answer_tokens": ["Like", "said", ",", "because", ",", "you", "know", ",", "the", "onus", "is", "on", "--", "is", "on", "Oscar", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "And will you be seeing him if he does?", "question_tokens": ["And", "will", "you", "be", "seeing", "him", "if", "he", "does", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "That's up to the state obviously.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "up", "to", "the", "state", "obviously", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "How significant could that be?", "question_tokens": ["How", "significant", "could", "that", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "IN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "Well, it's possible.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "possible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "Do you think he should get bail?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "he", "should", "get", "bail", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "I don't think he should get bail.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "he", "should", "get", "bail", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "Do you really believe that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "really", "believe", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "We know he's responsible for the death.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "know", "he", "'s", "responsible", "for", "the", "death", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "Fine, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Fine", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "But, I mean, if an American president retired on the grounds of exhaustion, they'd be ridiculed, wouldn't they?", "question_tokens": ["But", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "if", "an", "American", "president", "retired", "on", "the", "grounds", "of", "exhaustion", ",", "they", "'d", "be", "ridiculed", ",", "would", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "Well, I think it was not only exhaustion, but he said that he was just not mentally able to handle the challenges that were required of his job, which is an enormous job.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "was", "not", "only", "exhaustion", ",", "but", "he", "said", "that", "he", "was", "just", "not", "mentally", "able", "to", "handle", "the", "challenges", "that", "were", "required", "of", "his", "job", ",", "which", "is", "an", "enormous", "job", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "Do you take that as a compliment, or is it kind of a veiled insult?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "take", "that", "as", "a", "compliment", ",", "or", "is", "it", "kind", "of", "a", "veiled", "insult", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "Well, I take it as a compliment.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "take", "it", "as", "a", "compliment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "Has the role of president changed dramatically, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "the", "role", "of", "president", "changed", "dramatically", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "I mean, when you look at the challenges facing President Obama and the way it now works in the modern age, what do you think of it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "when", "you", "look", "at", "the", "challenges", "facing", "President", "Obama", "and", "the", "way", "it", "now", "works", "in", "the", "modern", "age", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "It's changed dramatically.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "changed", "dramatically", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ronald Reagan"]}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "RBR", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "Seriously?", "question_tokens": ["Seriously", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "When I ran four years later against Ronald Reagan, who was challenging me, we didn't raise any money.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "I", "ran", "four", "years", "later", "against", "Ronald", "Reagan", ",", "who", "was", "challenging", "me", ",", "we", "did", "n't", "raise", "any", "money", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "Extraordinary, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Extraordinary", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "So the change has been brought about, it's primarily because of a massive infusion of money into the political campaign.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "the", "change", "has", "been", "brought", "about", ",", "it", "'s", "primarily", "because", "of", "a", "massive", "infusion", "of", "money", "into", "the", "political", "campaign", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "Does that corrupt the political system?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "corrupt", "the", "political", "system", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "It corrupts the whole political system.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "corrupts", "the", "whole", "political", "system", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "What do you think has been the greatest achievement, and what do you think has been his greatest failure to date, and what would you like to see him do in this second term?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "has", "been", "the", "greatest", "achievement", ",", "and", "what", "do", "you", "think", "has", "been", "his", "greatest", "failure", "to", "date", ",", "and", "what", "would", "you", "like", "to", "see", "him", "do", "in", "this", "second", "term", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "NN", ",", "CC", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "Well, I think in his second term, he'll obviously have to be a lot more liberated from political constraints than he was before.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "in", "his", "second", "term", ",", "he", "'ll", "obviously", "have", "to", "be", "a", "lot", "more", "liberated", "from", "political", "constraints", "than", "he", "was", "before", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "And I said, what about his greatest and worst moments as president, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["And", "I", "said", ",", "what", "about", "his", "greatest", "and", "worst", "moments", "as", "president", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "WP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "Well, I wouldn't -- I don't think he's had a worst moment.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "n't", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "he", "'s", "had", "a", "worst", "moment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "Are any drone attacks acceptable?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "any", "drone", "attacks", "acceptable", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "I can't disavow all of the drone attacks, but I would really like to see some intermediate step.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "ca", "n't", "disavow", "all", "of", "the", "drone", "attacks", ",", "but", "I", "would", "really", "like", "to", "see", "some", "intermediate", "step", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obamacare"]}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "What have been his great achievements?", "question_tokens": ["What", "have", "been", "his", "great", "achievements", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "Well, I think -- I think everybody says Obamacare or the new health program is a major achievement.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "--", "I", "think", "everybody", "says", "Obamacare", "or", "the", "new", "health", "program", "is", "a", "major", "achievement", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 297, "question": "Have things improved or deteriorated, or are they about the same?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "things", "improved", "or", "deteriorated", ",", "or", "are", "they", "about", "the", "same", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 298, "answer": "About the same.", "answer_tokens": ["About", "the", "same", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "JJ", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "And did he actually say thank you for winning me the election?", "question_tokens": ["And", "did", "he", "actually", "say", "thank", "you", "for", "winning", "me", "the", "election", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "I don't think he said, winning the election, but thank you for helping me win the election.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "he", "said", ",", "winning", "the", "election", ",", "but", "thank", "you", "for", "helping", "me", "win", "the", "election", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "Final question for this part, do you think Hillary Clinton is going to run in 2016?", "question_tokens": ["Final", "question", "for", "this", "part", ",", "do", "you", "think", "Hillary", "Clinton", "is", "going", "to", "run", "in", "2016", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "I don't know, but she -- I think -- let me just say that I don't know what she's going to do, but she has done an outstanding job, I believe, as a secretary of state.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", ",", "but", "she", "--", "I", "think", "--", "let", "me", "just", "say", "that", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "she", "'s", "going", "to", "do", ",", "but", "she", "has", "done", "an", "outstanding", "job", ",", "I", "believe", ",", "as", "a", "secretary", "of", "state", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2016"], "PERSON": ["Hillary Clinton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "How accurate is it from your memory?", "question_tokens": ["How", "accurate", "is", "it", "from", "your", "memory", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "Well, let me say first of all, it's a great drama.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "let", "me", "say", "first", "of", "all", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "great", "drama", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "Had that third one not gone down, do you think it would have saved your presidency?", "question_tokens": ["Had", "that", "third", "one", "not", "gone", "down", ",", "do", "you", "think", "it", "would", "have", "saved", "your", "presidency", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "JJ", "CD", "RB", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Secret Service"], "LOCATION": ["Capitol", "Germany"], "PERSON": ["Reagan"]}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WRB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ":", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "How did you feel about that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "feel", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "That was one of the happiest moments of my life, when on the reviewing stand in front of the Capitol, when President Reagan was making his acceptance speech -- his inaugural speech -- I was told secretly by the Secret Service that the hostages had taken off, they were on their way to Germany, free.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "was", "one", "of", "the", "happiest", "moments", "of", "my", "life", ",", "when", "on", "the", "reviewing", "stand", "in", "front", "of", "the", "Capitol", ",", "when", "President", "Reagan", "was", "making", "his", "acceptance", "speech", "--", "his", "inaugural", "speech", "--", "I", "was", "told", "secretly", "by", "the", "Secret", "Service", "that", "the", "hostages", "had", "taken", "off", ",", "they", "were", "on", "their", "way", "to", "Germany", ",", "free", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "Did you agree with him?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "agree", "with", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "Is that a sensible way forward for America, to let the international community to take more of a lion's share of international incidents like in Libya, like in Egypt, whatever it may be?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "a", "sensible", "way", "forward", "for", "America", ",", "to", "let", "the", "international", "community", "to", "take", "more", "of", "a", "lion", "'s", "share", "of", "international", "incidents", "like", "in", "Libya", ",", "like", "in", "Egypt", ",", "whatever", "it", "may", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "Libya", "Egypt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "Should America be a little bit more insular, be more selfish?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "America", "be", "a", "little", "bit", "more", "insular", ",", "be", "more", "selfish", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "NNP", "VB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "JJR", "JJ", ",", "VB", "RBR", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "I don't think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "Does everything in the end come back to Israel and Palestine?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "everything", "in", "the", "end", "come", "back", "to", "Israel", "and", "Palestine", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "Yes, I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hamas"]}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "Can any deal be done that doesn't involve sitting across a table with Hamas?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "any", "deal", "be", "done", "that", "does", "n't", "involve", "sitting", "across", "a", "table", "with", "Hamas", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "I've met several times with Hamas' leadership.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "met", "several", "times", "with", "Hamas", "'", "leadership", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hamas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "But at what point should America consider military action, and what type of action would be acceptable, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["But", "at", "what", "point", "should", "America", "consider", "military", "action", ",", "and", "what", "type", "of", "action", "would", "be", "acceptable", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "WP", "NN", "MD", "NNP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "Well, I would hope that we could avoid military action there.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "hope", "that", "we", "could", "avoid", "military", "action", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", ":", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "What should be done about him?", "question_tokens": ["What", "should", "be", "done", "about", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "Well, I'm not sure that -- that what you just said is true, because I have always doubted that Assad could be overthrown in this sort of early stage.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "sure", "that", "--", "that", "what", "you", "just", "said", "is", "true", ",", "because", "I", "have", "always", "doubted", "that", "Assad", "could", "be", "overthrown", "in", "this", "sort", "of", "early", "stage", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "What do you make of this debate post the appalling atrocity in Sandy Hook?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "this", "debate", "post", "the", "appalling", "atrocity", "in", "Sandy", "Hook", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "Well, for a long time, I've advocated a prohibition against assault weapons and against magazines that hold multiple bullets and also armor-piercing bullets and things of that kind.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "for", "a", "long", "time", ",", "I", "'ve", "advocated", "a", "prohibition", "against", "assault", "weapons", "and", "against", "magazines", "that", "hold", "multiple", "bullets", "and", "also", "armor-piercing", "bullets", "and", "things", "of", "that", "kind", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House", "Congress"]}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 552, "question": "What should President Obama do to try and get through another assault-weapon ban?", "question_tokens": ["What", "should", "President", "Obama", "do", "to", "try", "and", "get", "through", "another", "assault-weapon", "ban", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "Well, you have to put the full, you know, influence of the White House behind a subject this controversial and deal with every senator and every Congress member on an individual basis and see what they need and what they want and maybe use, you know, most persuasive effort.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "have", "to", "put", "the", "full", ",", "you", "know", ",", "influence", "of", "the", "White", "House", "behind", "a", "subject", "this", "controversial", "and", "deal", "with", "every", "senator", "and", "every", "Congress", "member", "on", "an", "individual", "basis", "and", "see", "what", "they", "need", "and", "what", "they", "want", "and", "maybe", "use", ",", "you", "know", ",", "most", "persuasive", "effort", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "Has it become your greatest achievement, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "it", "become", "your", "greatest", "achievement", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJS", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Earth"]}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RBR", "NNS", "VBP", "RP", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "RB", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "Could you have cracked it?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "have", "cracked", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "Oh, well, we're going to have some more cases come up later on in the year, but we -- we're cutting down it, and eventually, very soon, we'll have zero cases of Guinea worm on Earth.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "well", ",", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "have", "some", "more", "cases", "come", "up", "later", "on", "in", "the", "year", ",", "but", "we", "--", "we", "'re", "cutting", "down", "it", ",", "and", "eventually", ",", "very", "soon", ",", "we", "'ll", "have", "zero", "cases", "of", "Guinea", "worm", "on", "Earth", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 590, "question": "How is she?", "question_tokens": ["How", "is", "she", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 591, "answer": "She's doing fine.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "doing", "fine", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "``", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNPS", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 597, "question": "If you could write your own tombstone, what would you like the wording to say?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "could", "write", "your", "own", "tombstone", ",", "what", "would", "you", "like", "the", "wording", "to", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "I think \"Peace and Human Rights.\"", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "``", "Peace", "and", "Human", "Rights", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]